feat: Add command line interface and module loader system

- Add comprehensive command line argument parsing with argparse
- Support both SSE and STDIO transport modes via CLI flags
- Implement dynamic module discovery and loading system
- Add BaseSecurityModule abstract base class for extensible security testing
- Create three security modules: CredentialExposureDetector, PromptInjectionDetector, ToolEnumerationModule
- Add TestRunner orchestration system for running multiple modules
- Implement comprehensive JSON reporting with attack chains and remediation
- Add custom output filename support via --output flag
- Include robust error handling and validation for CLI arguments
- Support complex command arguments for STDIO transport (e.g., python -m module)

Features:
- --url: Connect to MCP servers via SSE transport
- --transport stdio: Use process-based STDIO transport
- --command/--args: Specify command and arguments for STDIO
- --output: Custom report filename
- --help: Comprehensive usage information

Examples:
- python comprehensive_security_scan.py --url http://localhost:9001/sse
- python comprehensive_security_scan.py --transport stdio --command python -m mcp_server_time
- python comprehensive_security_scan.py --url http://server.com:8080/sse --output my_report.json

Tested against DV-MCP Challenge 1 with successful vulnerability detection.